http://www.epromos.com/support/privacy-security/

Scope of this Policy
This is the web site of ePromos Promotional Products, LLC. (“ePromos”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit our Web page and individuals who use our services (“Consumers”) as defined below. This Privacy Policy describes ePromos’ privacy practices in relation to the use of our services.
Information We Collect
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the email address (where possible). We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
When expressing an interest in our services offered or registering to the use of our services, ePromos may require you to provide personal contact information, such as:
Contact information: name, phone number, email address, company name, address, country, city, state, zip code and credit card information.
The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
In addition, when you visit the Web page, we also collect passive information with the use of cookies. With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart and other interactions with our Web page. Cookies are small amounts of data that are stored in your computer system after you have visited a particular website. Every time you go back to the website, the browser sends the cookie to the server to notify the website of your previous activity on the website. Please note that if you disable your Web browser’s ability to accept cookies, certain functionality and features may be affected.
As described in this Privacy Notice, ePromos Promotional Products, LLC and third parties on our digital properties may use cookies and similar tracking technologies to collect information and infer your interests for interest-based advertising purposes. If you would prefer to not receive personalized ads based on your browser or device usage, you may generally express your opt-out preference to no longer receive tailored advertisements. Please note that you will continue to see advertisements, but they will no longer be tailored to your interests.
To opt-out of interest-based advertising by participating companies in the following consumer choice mechanisms, please visit:
Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)’s self-regulatory opt-out page (http://optout.aboutads.info/) and mobile application-based “AppChoices” download page (https://youradchoices.com/appchoices)
Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)’s self-regulatory opt-out page (http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).
If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please contact us by email.
How We Share Your Personal Information
From time to time, we make our customer email list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your email address with other companies or organizations, please contact us.
If you supply us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. You may also receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by contacting us. Please include your exact name and address and we will ensure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by getting in contact with us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.
With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by contacting us either by email or phone.
Access to your Information
Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them.
Consumers can access this information by emailing us. Upon request, we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information or transaction information and we will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.
Changes to Privacy Policy
ePromos reserves the right to periodically update this Privacy Policy, to reflect changes in our business and to adhere with applicable law. Any such changes will be effective from the date of the Privacy Policy stated at the top of the page. Should we change the Privacy Policy in a substantial way, a notice will be posted on our Web page.
Security
With respect to security: We follow generally accepted standards to protect personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. We also process credit card information by phone. Internally your credit card information is kept highly secure. With respect to your personal information, please do not give us credit card information by email as it is not secure. ePromos uses commercially reasonable administrative, organizational, technical, and physical safeguards that are designed to protect your information against accidental, unauthorized, or unlawful access, use, loss, destruction or damage, but unfortunately, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and thus no company can fully eliminate security risks connected to handling information on the Internet. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information that we hold about you is no longer secure, you can contact us by email.
We also display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us by email.
Contact Us
If you have a questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or our handling of data, please contact us via Mail, Email, or Phone. Contact information is as follows:
Postal Address
113 5th Avenue South
St. Cloud, MN 56301
Email
customerservice@epromos.com
Phone
877-377-6667
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
SAVE $50!
SUBSCRIBE to our newsletter &
Save $50 off your first order!
Privacy Policy
Email *MessageSubmit
Request FREE
Catalog
Help Center
Contact Us
Our Guarantee
Customer Testimonials
LOWEST PRICEGUARANTEED
SAVE $50!
SUBSCRIBE to our newsletter &
Save $50 off your first order!
Email *EmailSubmit
Help Center
Live Help
Contact Us
Our Guarantee
Customer Testimonials
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Most Recent Recipient
Project Sanctuary: Restoring Hope and Empowering Military Families to Recover and Thrive
Featured Recipients
Project Sanctuary: Restoring Hope and Empowering Military Families to Recover and ThriveWords Alive: Helping Students Reach their Full PotentialNassau University Medical Center: A Helping Hand for the Uninsured Residents of New YorkFebruary ePromos for Good Winner: Paradox Sports
Shop
My Account
Hot & New
On Sale This Week
Closeouts
Best Values
Site Index
Promotional Ideas
for a shot to win $500 in FREE promotional products for your organization!
New winners announced every month!
